var results = {"results":[{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which%20company%20did%20Valve%20cooperate%20with%20in%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Vive%3F","correct_answer":"HTC","incorrect_answers":["Oculus","Google","Razer"]},
            {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20alcoholic%20drink%20is%20made%20from%20molasses%3F","correct_answer":"Rum","incorrect_answers":["Gin","Vodka","Whisky"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20nickname%20of%20the%20US%20state%20of%20California%3F","correct_answer":"Golden%20State","incorrect_answers":["Sunshine%20State","Bay%20State","Treasure%20State"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20on%20display%20in%20the%20Madame%20Tussaud%27s%20museum%20in%20London%3F","correct_answer":"Wax%20sculptures","incorrect_answers":["Designer%20clothing","Unreleased%20film%20reels","Vintage%20cars"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20was%20the%20nickname%20given%20to%20the%20Hughes%20H-4%20Hercules%2C%20a%20heavy%20transport%20flying%20boat%20which%20achieved%20flight%20in%201947%3F","correct_answer":"Spruce%20Goose","incorrect_answers":["Noah%27s%20Ark","Fat%20Man","Trojan%20Horse"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Five%20dollars%20is%20worth%20how%20many%20nickles%3F","correct_answer":"100","incorrect_answers":["50","25","69"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20depicted%20on%20the%20US%20hundred%20dollar%20bill%3F","correct_answer":"Benjamin%20Franklin","incorrect_answers":["George%20Washington","Abraham%20Lincoln","Thomas%20Jefferson"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20Tasmania%3F","correct_answer":"An%20Australian%20State","incorrect_answers":["A%20flavor%20of%20Ben%20and%20Jerry%27s%20ice-cream","A%20Psychological%20Disorder","The%20Name%20of%20a%20Warner%20Brothers%20Cartoon%20Character"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The%20likeness%20of%20which%20president%20is%20featured%20on%20the%20rare%20%242%20bill%20of%20USA%20currency%3F","correct_answer":"Thomas%20Jefferson","incorrect_answers":["Martin%20Van%20Buren","Ulysses%20Grant","John%20Quincy%20Adams"]},
         {"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How%20many%20furlongs%20are%20there%20in%20a%20mile%3F","correct_answer":"Eight","incorrect_answers":["Two","Four","Six"]}]};